[{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678850427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7942,"timeElapsed":17178},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678858242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7813,"timeElapsed":24993},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678862642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4398,"timeElapsed":29393},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678865709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3064,"timeElapsed":32460},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678869276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3564,"timeElapsed":36026},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678872976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3698,"timeElapsed":39727},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678875709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2730,"timeElapsed":42460},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678881492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5781,"timeElapsed":48243},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678884409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":51160},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678890626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5314,"timeElapsed":57377},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678893576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2947,"timeElapsed":60327},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678897650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4072,"timeElapsed":64401},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":66977},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678903776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3548,"timeElapsed":70527},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678906509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2731,"timeElapsed":73260},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678910660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4149,"timeElapsed":77411},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678914176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":80927},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678916359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":83110},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678926076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8230,"timeElapsed":92827},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678927609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1531,"timeElapsed":94360},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":96210},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678931126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":97877},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1998,"timeElapsed":99877},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678935126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1997,"timeElapsed":101877},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":104094},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1780,"timeElapsed":105877},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":107610},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678946526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4881,"timeElapsed":113277},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951125,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4597,"timeElapsed":117876},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5848,"timeElapsed":123726},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":125726},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1998,"timeElapsed":127726},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2331,"timeElapsed":130060},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2749,"timeElapsed":132810},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":134960},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2248,"timeElapsed":137210},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1632,"timeElapsed":138844},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678977659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4164,"timeElapsed":144409},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":146194},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1831,"timeElapsed":148027},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678983376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2098,"timeElapsed":150127},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678986626,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3247,"timeElapsed":153377},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3864,"timeElapsed":157244},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2264,"timeElapsed":159510},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":161727},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678997175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":163926},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1749,"timeElapsed":165676},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4364,"timeElapsed":171044},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":172894},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1798,"timeElapsed":174694},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":176310},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2631,"timeElapsed":178943},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2050,"timeElapsed":180995},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679016109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1863,"timeElapsed":182860},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2099,"timeElapsed":184961},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1514,"timeElapsed":186477},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4347,"timeElapsed":191660},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679026609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1698,"timeElapsed":193360},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679028776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2165,"timeElapsed":195527},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1515,"timeElapsed":197044},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1815,"timeElapsed":198861},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":201061},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1998,"timeElapsed":203060},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2015,"timeElapsed":205078},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":207277},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":8981,"timeElapsed":217311},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":1848,"timeElapsed":219161},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1981,"timeElapsed":221144},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1814,"timeElapsed":222961},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1864,"timeElapsed":224827},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":226777},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":228894},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679064077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":230828},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2414,"timeElapsed":233243},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679071710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4264,"timeElapsed":238461},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1631,"timeElapsed":240094},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2147,"timeElapsed":242243},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":243894},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":246327},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2032,"timeElapsed":248361},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1864,"timeElapsed":250227},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":251878},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679086677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1548,"timeElapsed":253428},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":256928},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1547,"timeElapsed":258478},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679093293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1564,"timeElapsed":260044},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1414,"timeElapsed":261461},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":264477},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1832,"timeElapsed":266311},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":268444},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":270661},{"subjectID":"tlcbosoqrs","prolificID":"66af9cb47a90d72488befa2c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b1ecc61b67917d25f1a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":272511}]